What's up guys? It's kil, iron here with another card commentary and that's as far as my impersonation goes I
Haven't worked on new video since the Pokemon video so I can go through this together. I hope you didn't expect something fancy
I thought I'd get about 20 questions not 200 but after removing all the pop-culture references
I was left with about 17. So here we go
Where are you from this is my most asked question and most people already know that I'm from Sweden
Yes, Sweden Mountains chocolate banks cheese, Etc
The second most asked question is is that the song from and yes?
It is every time why is your avatar a racoon?
I didn't want a real animal as my avatar so I took a picture of a raccoon then colored it red
using photoshop creating a new fantasy creature no nasty video game Racoon
Then I gave him a tricone hat because you know people would say my avatar
They would be like [oh] a trike or not man that channel must be an adventure dinosaurs or dragons
Dinosaurs because they are real who gives a shit about a fantasy animal that dies in the first four minutes of the movie?
Once again, that is Bullshit Peter Jackson
How much time does it take for you to create a ridiculous recap episode way too long most of the time is spent writing jokes?
Obviously different videos take a different amount of time the only video
I actually counted the hours was the Assassin's Creed 2 video and that took [49] hours
But that includes gameplay the warcraft
Retrospective took the longest to make and the dark souls video took the shortest amount of time when is the next q&A of this one?
Depends on how much hate this one gets
Alternative question does the fact that quantum field theory requires both charge and mass renormalization
to make the equations and
Operators actually be sensible mean that the universe just works that way or that are as of yet best efforts are unavoidably wrong
Incomplete you know that's a good question, but as I have only read seven books on Quantum field theory
I'm not 100% sure but I personally believe that quantum field theory are unable to do
Because some theories don't have mastery normalization and our
Education such as the mercury and the Iraq and such as our education
here should help the Asian countries q why can't you spell swedish in English by combining the colors one online [a]
Fucking would mate. Do you love me? I think was more as friends. How big is your steam library?
[I] have [twenty] games
And it's all german train simulators why our lobsters boiled alive and do they feel pain no idea?
So I went out and asked a lobster and here's my interview with a lobster I
Asked him, why are you boiled alive?
And he responded I don't know why did someone boil your face
So the recent lobsters are [both] [alive] is because they can't be roasted then I asked him if he feels pain
And he told me that physical pain is nothing compared to the pain of loneliness, and that's when I left
What is your favorite video game soundtrack and why it's not spyro, you're the fucking dragon
It's [Halo] dST because I think it's a great soundtrack from start to finish
But you will never hear it in one of my videos because [I] have too much respect for it, and that's a lie
I don't want to get a copyright strike. What is your favorite genre of game?
I checked my steam and my top 5 games in terms of playtime are all strategy games
I hate strategy games, so I don't know my favorite game genre, but it's not fucking strategy games
I prefer dog food human food got any tips
No
Why no?
Do you have any future plans for your channel? I am starting on a game of the [year] video tomorrow, and when that's done
[I'm] starting on the next recap
I can post videos like I have all throughout spring
No plans Beyond spring hopefully a new trend will come up like five nights at Freddy's
So that I can kneel to that and just abandon this I want to get better at Twitter because right now
I post like one joke between episodes
I'm hoping that I can at least post two in the future [so] and now the last [question]
What is the Kilian experience and that is the [Kirlian] experience?